atomox.net 2016-10-27

# Privacy Policy - SuperfastVPS, Super Fast Cloud web hosting and VPS Servers provider SuperfastVPS, Super Fast Cloud web hosting and VPS Servers provider

### Privacy Policy

At SuperFastVPS.com we are committed to safeguarding and preserving the privacy of our visitors.

This Policy explains what happens to any personal data that you provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit our site and how we use cookies on this website.

SuperFastVPS web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users’ privacy.

1. What personally identifiable information we collects.

2\. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.

3. What organization collects the information.

4. How SuperfastVPS uses the information.

5. With whom SuperfastVPS may share user information.

6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.

7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under SuperFastVPS control.

8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

Information Collection and Use  
Information Collection  
SuperfastVPS is the sole owner of the information collected on. SuperfastVPS collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**Registration**  
In order to use this Web site, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide demographic information (such as income level and gender), and unique identifiers (such as, username and password), but encouraged so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site.

**Order  Services**  
We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email,country,telephone) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order or service , the information is used to contact the user.

**Information Use**  
Use of SUPERFASTVPS Service constitutes acceptance and agreement to SUPERFASTVPS’s [AUP](http://superfastvps.com/about/legal/AUP) as well as SUPERFASTVPS ‘s [TOS ](http://superfastvps.com/about/legal/TOS/)(Terms of Service).

**Profile**  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them.  **We [do not] share your profile with other third parties.**

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. IP addresses are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web-based service.

**Offers and Updates**  
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

**Service Announcements**  
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, Users may opt-out of these communications. Please see our Choice and Opt-out section.

**Customer Service**  
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

We never give your details to third parties to use your data to enable them to provide you with information regarding unrelated goods or services.

**Choice/Opt-out**  
Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. For example, our order form has an ‘opt-out’ mechanism so users who buy a product from us, but don’t want any marketing material, can keep their email address off of our lists.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email.We also offer an opt-out mechanism on the member section or the user may contact us at to opt-out.

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party.

**Links**  
This web site does not contains links to other sites. SuperfastVPS is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Message Boards**  
Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online – for example on message boards, or blog  through e-mail, areas – that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

**Security**  
This web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number, that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Chrome and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment,all credit card information is encrypted, in order for someone to to read would need the de-encryption code. We use RC4 DATA ENCRYPTION we encrypts all credit card numbers before writing them to the database. The encryption/decryption used is RC4, providing another layer of protection.

Supplementation of Information  
In order for this web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information  
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done at the member information page.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by e-mail.

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](https://www.superfastvps.com/submitticket.php?step=2&deptid=4).

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should first contact us.
